{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following solutions would be best suited for a company that needs comprehensive IT services but lacks qualified IT personnel?",
      "options": ["MSA", "MaaS", "MSP", "MSSP"],
      "correct_answers": ["MSP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to a third-party vendor offering IT security management services?",
      "options": ["MSP", "MaaS", "MSA", "MSSP"],
      "correct_answers": ["MSSP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to the broad category of hardware and software systems used for monitoring and controlling physical devices, processes, and industrial operations?",
      "options": ["ICS", "OT", "SCADA", "EDR"],
      "correct_answers": ["OT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a basic method for establishing a dedicated point-to-point link between two networked devices?",
      "options": ["PPTP", "IGMP", "PPP", "MPLS"],
      "correct_answers": ["PPP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following defines the maximum acceptable amount of data loss measured by a specific point in time before a disaster or outage?",
      "options": ["RPO", "MTBF", "RTO", "MTTR"],
      "correct_answers": ["RPO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to a framework for managing access to digital resources?",
      "options": ["PAM", "SSO", "IAM", "MFA"],
      "correct_answers": ["IAM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refer to SCAP? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "A type of security system designed to collect logs and events from various sources",
        "Designed to provide a centralized user interface for accessing collected data",
        "A collection of standards developed by NIST",
        "Provides a common language for communicating security information",
        "Allows different security tools to share data and work together more effectively",
        "Enables real-time threat detection, incident response, and compliance monitoring"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "A collection of standards developed by NIST",
        "Provides a common language for communicating security information",
        "Allows different security tools to share data and work together more effectively"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A Windows feature used for centrally managing and enforcing policies and settings for users and computers in a network is referred to as:",
      "options": ["SAE", "NTLM", "GPO", "SSO"],
      "correct_answers": ["GPO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a protocol used for automating the issuance and management of certificates within a PKI environment?",
      "options": ["PKCS", "SCEP", "CSR", "OCSP"],
      "correct_answers": ["SCEP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refer to the characteristic features of RSA? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Asymmetric encryption algorithm",
        "A public key used for encryption and a private key used for decryption",
        "Suitable for bulk data encryption",
        "Used for secure communications, digital signatures, and key exchange",
        "Symmetric encryption algorithm",
        "A single key used for both encryption and decryption"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Asymmetric encryption algorithm",
        "A public key used for encryption and a private key used for decryption",
        "Used for secure communications, digital signatures, and key exchange"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below describe the characteristics of a non-persistent VDI? (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": [
        "At the end of a session, user desktop reverts to its original state",
        "Each user runs their own copy of virtual desktop",
        "At the end of a session, user data and personal settings are saved",
        "Virtual desktop is shared among multiple users"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "At the end of a session, user desktop reverts to its original state",
        "Virtual desktop is shared among multiple users"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an obsolete protocol used for secure data transfer over the web?",
      "options": ["SMTPS", "SRTP", "SHTTP", "S/MIME"],
      "correct_answers": ["SHTTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In a persistent VDI: (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Each user runs their own copy of virtual desktop",
        "At the end of a session, user desktop reverts to its original state",
        "Virtual desktop is shared among multiple users",
        "At the end of a session, user data and personal settings are saved"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Each user runs their own copy of virtual desktop",
        "At the end of a session, user data and personal settings are saved"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "An authentication mechanism that generates one-time passwords based on a counter value and a secret key is known as:",
      "options": ["OAuth", "HOTP", "RADIUS", "TOTP"],
      "correct_answers": ["HOTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a documented process for addressing identified issues and preventing their repetition?",
      "options": ["DRP", "COOP", "QA", "CAR"],
      "correct_answers": ["CAR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a software tool designed to simplify the process of creating and maintaining online content?",
      "options": ["VDI", "SaaS", "CMS", "SDK"],
      "correct_answers": ["CMS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which block cipher mode combines CTM for encryption with an authentication mechanism to ensure both data confidentiality and integrity?",
      "options": ["CBC", "GCM", "ECB", "CFB"],
      "correct_answers": ["GCM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"FPGA\" refers to a reconfigurable integrated circuit that can be programmed and customized to perform various digital functions and tasks.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to SIEM? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Allows different security tools to share data and work together more effectively",
        "Designed to provide a centralized user interface for accessing collected data",
        "A collection of standards developed by NIST",
        "Enables real-time threat detection, incident response, and compliance monitoring",
        "A type of security system designed to collect logs and events from various sources",
        "Provides a common language for communicating security information"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Designed to provide a centralized user interface for accessing collected data",
        "Enables real-time threat detection, incident response, and compliance monitoring",
        "A type of security system designed to collect logs and events from various sources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a trusted third-party service for validating user identity in a federated identity system?",
      "options": ["RA", "IdP", "CA", "Kerberos"],
      "correct_answers": ["IdP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a deprecated TLS-based method for securing SMTP?",
      "options": ["IDPS", "STARTTLS", "DKIM", "SMTPS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SMTPS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following enables running macros in Microsoft Office applications?",
      "options": ["DOM", "API", "DLL", "VBA"],
      "correct_answers": ["VBA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a language used to structure and describe data in a format that is both human- and machine-readable?",
      "options": ["HTML", "XML", "JSON", "XHTML"],
      "correct_answers": ["XML"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In SNMP, each node in a MIB is uniquely identified by a(n):",
      "options": ["OID", "IP", "OUI", "MAC"],
      "correct_answers": ["OID"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to a block cipher mode that works by chaining the ciphertext blocks together, such that each ciphertext block depends on the previous block?",
      "options": ["CBC", "GCM", "ECB", "CFB"],
      "correct_answers": ["CBC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a dedicated protocol designed for enabling real-time text-based communication over the Internet?",
      "options": ["IRC", "RTC", "IM", "MMS"],
      "correct_answers": ["IRC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A specialized electronic component that accelerates visual rendering is called:",
      "options": ["TPU", "GPU", "DSP", "CPU"],
      "correct_answers": ["GPU"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a protocol that enables the exchange of messages and data between applications running on different OSs and using different programming languages?",
      "options": ["VDE", "SOAP", "VDI", "SMTP"],
      "correct_answers": ["SOAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a deprecated MS Windows authentication protocol replaced by Kerberos?",
      "options": ["PPTP", "WEP", "NTLM", "SNMPv2"],
      "correct_answers": ["NTLM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following enables delivery of various data packet types over the same network link?",
      "options": ["LWAPP", "MPLS", "MLPPP", "MIBS"],
      "correct_answers": ["MPLS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a Windows-specific feature for handling exceptions, errors, and abnormal conditions in software?",
      "options": ["EPC", "SEH", "EH", "EXR"],
      "correct_answers": ["SEH"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to a security mechanism used in the DNS to authenticate and secure communications between DNS servers during zone transfers and other transactions?",
      "options": ["SOA", "DKIM", "SPF", "TSIG"],
      "correct_answers": ["TSIG"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a cable rack that interconnects wiring between an MDF and workstation devices?",
      "options": ["ICS", "MDI", "IDF", "MTU"],
      "correct_answers": ["IDF"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following technologies enables automated handling of multiple security incidents?",
      "options": ["SOAP", "SIEM", "SOAR", "SASE"],
      "correct_answers": ["SOAR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a solution that increases the efficiency of IP address space management by allowing network administrators to divide networks into subnets of different sizes?",
      "options": ["DNAT", "VLSM", "MPLS", "VLAN"],
      "correct_answers": ["VLSM"]
    }
  ]
}